amazonservices.com 2008-11-11

# Amazon Business Solutions - Privacy Policy

  * Selling on Amazon
  * Amazon Payments
  * Product Ads on Amazon
  * WebStore by Amazon
  * Fulfillment by Amazon
  * Drop Ship by Amazon 
  * Corporate Accounts at Amazon 

| 

Last updated: December 1, 2005

December 1, 2005 

Amazon Services knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. **By visiting www.amazonservices.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

**What Personal Information About Users Does Amazon Services Gather?**

The information we learn from users helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at www.amazonservices.com. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. Click here to see examples of what we collect. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, improving the site, and communicating with you. 
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses www.amazonservices.com. Click here to see examples of the information we receive. A number of [companies](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/browse/-/501098/002-0524907-7464825) offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at www.amazonservices.com if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist. 
  * **E-mail Communications:** To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Amazon Services if your computer supports such capabilities. 
  * **Information from Other Sources:** We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our information. Click here to see examples of the information we receive. 

* * *

#### What About Cookies?

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide various features. 
  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, you may not be able to use certain features on this site if you do not use cookies, and we recommend that you keep them turned on.

* * *

#### Does Amazon Services Share the Information It Receives?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below and with Amazon.com, Inc. and the subsidiaries it controls that either are subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice.

  * **Use of Third Party Service Providers:** We may, from time to time, employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include sending postal mail and e-mail. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 
  * **Promotional Offers:** Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of Amazon Services customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. 
  * **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, user information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the user consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Amazon Services, Inc., or substantially all of its assets are acquired, user information will of course be one of the transferred assets. 
  * **Protection of Amazon Services and Others:** We release personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Amazon Services, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 
  * **With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 

* * *

#### What Choices and Access Do I Have?

  * As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to request information about Amazon Services or take advantage of a feature on this site.
  * If you do not want to receive Conditions of Use and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of www.amazonservices.com, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.
  * If you do not want to accept cookies, please use the Help portion of the toolbar on your browser to disable cookies. Please see "What About Cookies?" above for more information.
  * [Click here](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/browse/-/501098/002-0524907-7464825) to explore products that offer anonymous browsing. 

* * *

#### What About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Web sites?

Our site may include third-party advertising and links to other Web sites. These Web sites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our site directly to your browser. They may also use cookies, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), javascript, and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party Web sites. Further, we do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party Web sites are not covered by this privacy notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. In addition, the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) offers useful information about Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"), including information about how to opt-out of their information collection.

* * *

#### Children

Amazon Services, and its Web site www.amazonservices.com, is not intended for use by children under the age of 18.? If you are under 18, you may not submit information about yourself to www.amazonservices.com.

* * *

#### Safe Harbor

Amazon Services is an Amazon.com company.? Amazon.com is a participant in the Safe Harbor program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles agreed upon by the U.S. and the E.U. For more information about the Safe Harbor and to view our certification, visit the [U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/) Web site. If you would like to contact Amazon.com directly about the Safe Harbor program, please send an e-mail to [safeharbor@amazon.com](mailto:safeharbor@amazon.com).

* * *

#### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit www.amazonservices.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the State of Washington. If you have any concern about privacy at Amazon Services, please [contact us](mailto:info@amazonservices.com) with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. 

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected users. 

* * *

#### Related Practices and Information 

  * Terms of Use
  * **Amazon.com Privacy Policy and Conditions of Use:**? If you choose to sell through the Amazon.com platform, your visits to the Amazon.com site, including any disputes over privacy arising out of that activity, will be governed by the Amazon.com Conditions of Use, and the Amazon.com Privacy Policy.

* * *

#### Examples of Information Collected

**Information You Give Us**

You provide most such information when you use www.amazonservices.com to request information about Amazon Services or otherwise communicate with us. For example, you provide information when you submit requests for information via this site; communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; and employ our other services.

**Automatic Information**

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; pages you viewed or searched for, and the phone number you used to call us.? During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

**Information from Other Sources**

An example of information we receive from other sources includes information we obtain from third party industry web sites. 

|
